Guide to the Bunnell Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Personal, Household, and Business Records, 1758-1924; Series III; 1 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Lambert and Bunnell, Architects
    - Account books relating to property on State St., Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1872-1879 (Box 18, Folder 337)
    - Journal of expenditures, 1861-1901 (Box 18, Folder 338)
    - Receipt book, 1861-1901 (Box 18, Folder 339)
    - Records relating to property on State St., Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1872, 1873-1880, 1889, undated (Box 18, Folder 340-342)
  - Dr. Agur Tomlinson: Last will and testament, 1773 (Box 18, Folder 343)
  - Phebe Lewis Tomlinson: Last will and testament, 1840 (Box 18, Folder 344)
  - Dr. William Agur Tomlinson: Inventory; medical certificates; Sociable Club document, 1772, 1785-1786, undated (Box 18, Folder 345)
  - Zachariah Tomlinson and Jemima Skidmore: Marriage contract, 1758 (Box 18, Folder 346)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1831, 1847, 1866, 1871, 1901-1905, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 347)
- Writings, 1832-1950; Series IV; 1 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell
    - "The Stratford Academy, 1804-1876", 1931 (Box 19, Folder 348)
    - Untitled poem, undated (Box 19, Folder 348)
  - Frank S. Bunnell
    - "Log of a Trip from Fourth Lake Beyond Lake Placid...", 1899 (Box 19, Folder 349)
    - Log of unspecified trip, 1898 (Box 19, Folder 349)
    - Yale course notes, 1892-1893, 1894, undated (Box 19, Folder 350-351)
  - Frank S. Bunnell and Sterling H. Bunnell
    - The Stratfordite, 1885-1886 (Box 19, Folder 352)
  - Rufus W. Bunnell
    - "Connecticut Style of Dwellings", 1856 (Box 19, Folder 353)
    - "The Early Architectural History of the City of Bridgeport...", 1906 (Box 19, Folder 353)
    - The Life of William Rufus Bunnell, 1906 (Box 19, Folder 354)
    - The Life of William Rufus Bunnell (photocopy), 1906 (Box 19, Folder 355)
    - "My trip to Europe in 1907-1908", undated (Box 19, Folder 356)
    - "Some personal experiences in the South...", 1907 (Box 19, Folder 357)
    - Untitled autobiographical account, 1907 (Box 19, Folder 357)
      - Pages 1-50 (Box 19, Folder 358)
      - Pages 51-100 (Box 19, Folder 359)
      - Pages 101-150 (Box 20, Folder 360)
      - Pages 151-197 (Box 20, Folder 361)
  - [J. G. Shearman]
    - "Ascent of Vesuvius in 1872" (original and photocopy), undated (Box 20, Folder 362)
  - Catharine T. (Plant) Sterling
    - Student notes and essays, 1832 (Box 20, Folder 363)
  - Cordelia Sterling
    - Composition book, 1862 (Box 20, Folder 364)
  - Genealogical notes by various family members
    - Bunnell Family, undated (Box 20, Folder 365-366)
    - Day Family, Circa 1940, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 367)
    - Haight Family, Circa 1860-1870 (Box 20, Folder 368)
    - Strong Family, undated (Box 20, Folder 369)
- Scrapbooks, Albums and Memorabilia, 1858-[1953?]; Series V; 1 linear feet (3 boxes)
  This series contains material arranged alphabetically by creator and by type of material.
  - Frank S. Bunnell
    - Scrapbook, 1889-1894 (Box 21, Folder 370)
    - Scrapbook, 1894-1903 (Box 22, Folder 371)
    - Scrapbook material, 1894-1911, 1903-1905 (Box 23, Folder 372-373)
    - European postcard album, 1900 (Box 23, Folder 374)
  - Rufus W. Bunnell
    - Scrapbook, 1858 (Box 23, Folder 375)
  - Clippings, 1894, 1899, 1905, 1907, 1938, undated (Box 23, Folder 376)
  - Notebook of book listings, undated (Box 23, Folder 377)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilia, 1860, 1864, 1867, 1885, 1894, 1896, 1930, [1953?] (Box 23, Folder 378)
- Photographs, Prints, and Drawings, 1849-1907; Series VI; .5 linear feet (2 boxes)
  This series contains material arranged by type of material.
  - Individual and group photographs
    See also: box 25, folder 1
  - Architectural materials
    - Residences designed by Lambert and Bunnell, 1854, 1856, 1860, 1862, 1880 (Box 24, Folder 390)
    - Lambert and Bunnell letterbox sign and envelope, undated (Box 24, Folder 390)
    - Sterling homestead photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 391)
    - Snapshot of fireplace in George Worman home (originally enclosed with undated letter from Helen Worman to Katherine [sic] Mitchell in box 14, folder 312) (Box 24, Folder 391)
  - Travel photographs from trip of Cordelia Sterling (originally enclosed with letter dated 1907 Jan 6 from Cordelia Sterling to her sister Catharine in box 7, folder 159) (Box 24, Folder 392)
  - Daguerreotypes
    - Catharine Mary (Sterling) Bunnell, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Catharine T. (Plant) Sterling, 1860 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cordelia Sterling, 1849,1857 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - Captain John W. Sterling, 1850 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - John W. Sterling, [1850] (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Letters of John W. Sterling
  The following is a list of John W. Sterling letters which formed the major part of accession number 86-M-52. While this is not a complete list of all John W. Sterling letters within the Bunnell Family Papers, it will enable users to access the majority of John W. Sterling letters within the collection.
  - Catharine M. Sterling, [1858 or 1859]
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 September 17
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 September 25
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 October 1
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 October 9
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 October 28
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1858 November 13
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1859 February
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1859 October
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1859 October 7
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1860 September 20
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1860 November 1
  - Capt. John W. Sterling, 1860 November 18
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1860 December
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 February 6
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 March 24
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 June 8
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 July 19
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 September 14
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1861 October
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 October 16
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 October 19
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 October 20
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 November 20
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1861 November 23
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1862 February 16
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1862 March 12
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1862 July 12
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1862 September 20
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1862 November 25
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1862 December 9
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1863 January
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1863 March 4
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1863 March 11
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1863 July 18
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1863 September 26
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1864 January 18
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1864 February
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1864 March 11
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1864 April
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1864 May 21
  - Capt. John W. Sterling, 1864 June 2
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1864 September 24
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 January 8
  - Sterling Family, 1865 January 9
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 February 26
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 April 2
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 July
  - Catharine T. (Plant) Sterling, 1865 October 7
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 October 20
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1865 November 26
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1866 January 28
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1866 July 15
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1866 August 5
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1866 August 19
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1866 September 2
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1866 December 9
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1867 February
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1867 February
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1867 February 10
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1868 April 29
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1868 May 15
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1868 October 25
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1868 November 15
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1868 December 7
  - Catharine M. and Cordelia Sterling, 1868 December 11
  - Catharine M. and Cordelia Sterling, 1868 December 13
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1868 December 20
  - Catharine M. Sterling, 1869 (fragment)
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1870 January 2
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1871 January 31
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 April 16
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 April 30
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 May 14
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 May 17
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 May 21
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 May 28
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 May 31
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 June 7
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 June 11
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 June 14
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 June 18
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1872 July 10
  - My dear Sister", 1873 May 10 (fragment)
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1876 December 23
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1877 February 17
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1877 May 3
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1877 June 7
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1877 June 25
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1877 November 13
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1877 December 24
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1878 March 18
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1879 June 18
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1880 January 23
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1880 August 12
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1880 December 24
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1881 April 1
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1881 April 2
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1892 June 6
  - [Cordelia Sterling], 1895 September 25
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1895 November 4
  - Catharine T. Bunnell, 1900 August 29
  - Catharine T. Bunnell, 1902 October 22
  - Catharine T. (Plant) Sterling, 1904 May 8
  - Cordelia Sterling, 1905 February 21
  - Catharine M. (Sterling) Bunnell, 1905 June 9
  - Catharine T. Bunnell, 1909 December 31
  - Catharine T. (Bunnell) Mitchell, 1916 October 25
  - Catharine T. (Bunnell) Mitchell, 1918 June 27